稍息 士兵
At ease, soldier.
你不会超车啊 蠢货！
Go around, you jerk.
这不是普通的暴走族
That's no road rage.
有人想撞死我…
Someone's trying to bump me off.
…擎天柱？
Prime?
擎天柱！你的铁头生锈了？
Prime, have you flipped your metal wig?
哈哈 很好！
- Haha...\N- Yes!
快点！快点！快点！
Go! Go! Go!
全速前进 神子
Metal to the pedal, Miko.
快开 杰克 快开！
Go, Jack, go!
不可能！拉夫完胜我们了！
No way! Raf's scorching us.
擎天柱？听到了吗？
Prime? Do you read me?
我很抱歉 福特探员
I'm sorry, Agent Fowler.
擎天柱此刻正好不在
Optimus isn't here at the moment.
那么这正好说明
Then I'll take that asa confirmation
想把我撞飞的就是他
that he's presently trying to run me off the road!
福勒探员 这不太可能
Agent Fowler, that hardly seems likely.
这话你跟我快烧焦的轮胎说吧！
Tell that to my burning treads!
快！快点！
Come on. Come on...
擎天柱！不要！
Prime, no!
看着是挺像擎天柱
Looks like Optimus.
领袖们才不会逃跑
Primes don't run.
你还好吗？
You all right in there?
稍息 士兵
At ease, soldier.
很好 就这样 跟着这道光
Yes, that's it. Follow the light.
啊 等等 什么？
Wait. What?
你这样说吓死我了 救护车
Not the best choice of words, Ratchet.
阿尔茜 你还好吗？
Arcee, are you all right?
当然 除了被擎天柱偷袭了一下
Sure. Except for being blindsided by Optimus.
我没骗你们吧！？
Didn't I tell you?
难以置信！
Impossible.
我只是在汇报我的所见所闻
I'm only reporting what I saw.
擎天柱为什么要撞死福勒探员？
Why would Optimus try to knock off Agent Fowler?
嗯 或许擎天柱又认为自己是霸天虎了
Maybe Optimus believes he's a Decepticon all over again.
或者他这段时间只是假装好人！
Or he's been faking being a good guy all this time.
不管擎天柱为了何种理由而行为越轨
If Prime has gone off the rails for any reason
我们都有麻烦了
we have a serious problem.
太荒谬了！
This is absurd.
对擎天柱的信号监测表明
A quick check for Optimus' signal will reveal
他今晚压根不在事发现场
that he's nowhere near the location of tonight's incident.
事实上 他正要返回基地
In fact, he's just returning now.
出什么事了吗？
Is something wrong?
我们只是…
We were just...
…想知道你去哪儿了？
wondering where you've been.
我们无法联系上你
We haven't been able to reach you.
我的位置超出了我们的通讯范围
I have been outside of our communication range...
- 哇哦！\N- 别冲动！
- Whoa.\N- Easy.
在一个地下能量矿中
... in a subterranean Energon deposit.
得了吧 他是自己人 不是吗？
Come on. It's our guy. Can't you tell?
我们…很抱歉
We're... sorry.
不要责备他们 擎天柱
Don't blame them, Prime.
今晚早些时候 我被袭击了
I was attacked earlier tonight
某人将我撞出了高速公路
out on the open highway by a big rig--
而它与你惊人地相似
one that bore a striking resemblance to you.
停下！
Halt!
这里是军事禁区
This is a restricted area.
立刻下车 否则我们开火了！
Exit the vehicle, or we will open fire.
我是擎天柱 汽车人的首领
I am Optimus Prime, leader of the autobots.
我来向你们传达一个信息
And I bring you this message.
我是福勒
Fowler.
什么？
What?!
那不可能！
That's not possible.
我以我短裤上的五十个星星打赌
I can tell you sure as there are 50 stars on my star-spangled shorts
那不是他！
it isn't him!
奥列尼军事基地被擎天柱袭击了！
Alden military base is under attack... by Optimus Prime.
那个卡车？
The truck?
机器人！
The 'Bot.
开火！开火！
Fire! Fire!
在那儿！他搬来了援军！继续开火！
There. They brought reinforcements. Resume fire!
汽车人 返回基地
Autobots, return to base.
我们必须避免伤及人类
We must not inflict human casualties.
不 布莱斯将军
No, General Bryce.
擎天柱没有攻击我们的人
Optimus Prime did not attack our boys.
当我收到警报时 擎天柱就站在我身边！
Because I was with Prime when I received the alert.
是的 长官 汽车人去了你的基地
Yes, sir. The Autobots were at your base
但那只是为了应对刚才的袭击
but only in response to the initial attack.
但是 长官 我…是的 长官 我明白了
But, sir, I... Yes, sir. I understand.
这次损失有多大？
So, what's the damage?
所有军队进入一级戒备
All military personnel are under strict orders
对所有的机器人 格杀勿论
to destroy any and all 'Bots on sight.
你开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding?!
他们是无辜的
But th-they're innocent.
擎天柱被陷害了！
Optimus was framed!
这很不幸
Though unfortunate
但是这种命令不能解决问题
the military order changes nothing.
那个冒牌货显然给人类造成了巨大的威胁
Our imposter clearly poses a grave threat to humanity.
一个三十英尺高的变形冒牌货
A 30-foot-tall transforming imposter.
他们真的完成了
They actually did it.
那些屠夫设法破译了代码
Those butchers managed to crack the code.
机械党
M.E.C.H.
长官 有视差或其他潜在问题吗？
Sir, any parallax or latency issues?
不管是汽车还是机器人形态
The telepresence interface performed flawlessly
远程操控界面都非常地完美
in vehicular and robot mode.
机械党劫持了打击
M.E.C.H. abducted Breakdown...
他们把他从头到脚都拆了个遍
and by all indications deconstructed him from cranial chamber to heel strut.
我亲眼所见
I was there.
而且我们最近得知
And we know that, more recently
他们获得了红蜘蛛的变形齿轮
they obtained Starscream's T-cog.
显然 他们将它安在了冒牌货身上
Which they evidently installed in a knockoff of you.
使他能扫描一个合适的车型
Which, in turn, scanned an appropriate vehicle form.
再填满能量仓
Fill the tank with Energon...
然后黑暗擎天柱就诞生了！
... and say hello to Nemesis Prime.
我们要从哪儿开始？
So, where do we start?
我们根本不知道机械党在哪儿
M.E.C.H.'s base could be anywhere.
别担心
Not necessarily.
尽管机械党了解了我们的生理构造
While M.E.C.H. may have learned much of our biology...
但他们还没有完全掌握我们的技术
They haven't necessarily absorbed our technology.
没有我们的环陆桥
Without access to a Ground Bridge
黑暗擎天柱只能靠车轮子来回奔波
Nemesis Prime would rely solely on its vehicle mode for transportation.
机械党的据点很可能就在两个事故现场的行车范围以内
Chances are the M.E.C.H. base is within driving distance of both incidents.
那我们还等什么？
What are we waiting for?
去把机械党的小小科技项目砸个稀巴烂吧！
Let's get out there and mash M.E.C.H's little science project.
福勒探员 我不建议你再次置身于
Agent Fowler, I do not think it advisable to put yourself
机械党的机器人所带来的危险之中
in harm's way of M.E.C.H's robot again.
好吧 我也不建议汽车人\N再次跑出去当军队的靶子
Well, I'm not sure it's advisable for 'Bots to be running recon with the military out there gunning for you.
我们会保持汽车形态 除非发生紧急情况
We will maintain vehicular cover until absolutely necessary.
除了杂草什么都没有
Nothing but tumbleweeds.
一片空旷
Just a whole lot of empty.
大黄蜂 你要加倍小心
Bumblebee, proceed with utmost caution.
只许侦查 不许交战 我们会在指定地点与你会合
Reconnaissance only. We will rendezvous at your coordinates.
顽固不化的汽车人
The Autobots are persistent.
他们的对手该登场了
Time to meet their match.
大黄蜂
Bumblebee.
保持警惕
Be on your guard.
冒牌货随时可能出现…
My double could be anywhere.
…抱歉 你说什么？
I'm sorry. What?
大黄蜂 收到了吗？
Bumblebee. Do you read?
散开？
Fan out?
小心任何跟我相似的东西
And beware of anything that might resemble me.
如果我能分离出塞拉斯的遥控信号
If I can isolate the control frequency of the remote link Silas is employing
我就能精确定位出他的位置
I should be able to pinpoint his exact position.
遥控？
Remote link?
难道你觉得机械党有高超的技术
You didn't think M.E.C.H. possessed the ability
去制造一个有自我意识的机器人吗？
to build a completely autonomous robot, did you?
我倒希望塞拉斯正躲在内部进行控制
I was hoping Silas would be operating the 'Bot from inside
这样隔板一拳下去就可以 呼呀！
because one punch from Bulkhead, and booyah!
啊哈！信号锁定！
Aha! Frequency isolated.
那就打开环陆桥
Then reopen that bridge.
福勒探员 你没听到擎天柱拒绝你参与进来吗？
Agent Fowler, did you not hear Optimus advise against your involvement?
这关系到你的安全！
It's for your own safety.
听着 医生 我没打算和机器人打架
Look, doc, I don't plan on dancing with any 'Bots
但是那里有人类参与其中
but there's a human element in play here
也许你还不知道
and in case you haven't noticed
我是一名受过特殊训练的 政府级别的 人类
I happen to be a highly trained, government-grade, human.
没错 塞拉斯曾想把他撞飞 这是私人恩怨
Yeah. Plus Silas tried to run him off the road, It's personal.
擎天柱 我们又见面了
Optimus Prime. We meet again.
你的骗局到此为止了 塞拉斯
The deception ends here, Silas.
是这样吗？
Does it?
我连在飞行学校吃的早餐都要吐出来了
I think I'm gonna toss the breakfast I ate back in flight school.
福勒探员 遥控信号的发射源
Agent Fowler, the control frequency is transmitting
在正北100米处的建筑中
from a structure 100 meters due north.
收到了
Copy that.
我的机器人完全复制了你的力量 速度还有火力
My robot chassis possesses all your strength, speed, and firepower.
并且融入了我的格斗技艺
Add my extensive combat training
机械党已经将人类和机器完美地融合在一起
and M.E.C.H. has clearly achieved the perfect meld of man and machine.
知道你我之间的主要差异在哪儿吗？
But the key difference between you and me?
我的身体感觉不到疼痛！
My body can't feel pain!
这只是个开始
This is just the beginning.
想象一下变形机器人组成的军队
Imagine an army of transforming robots.
没有人能对抗涅重生的机械党
No one will stand against the newly rebooted M.E.C.H.
再考虑下吧 小塞同志
Think again, Si.
福勒探员 你到底亲自出马了
Agent Fowler in the flesh at last.
我要拔掉你那游戏机的电源！
And I'm pulling the plug on your video game.
你是军人出身？
Ex-military?
特种战术部队 你呢？
Special tactics. You?
游骑兵团
Army rangers.
很明显 已经退役了
Retired, clearly.
虽然有点儿发福
I may be out of shape
但我不需要打倒你！
but I don't need to bust you up.
我只是为擎天柱争取点时间
I just need to buy Prime a little time.
不 不！
No. No!
不 不 不！
No! No! Nooo!
福勒探员？
Agent Fowler?
那些是我们的人
That would be our boys.
你最好返回基地 擎天柱
I advise you to get back to base, Prime.
我来应付山姆大叔
I'll handle Uncle Sam.
一个很像擎天柱的人把你打趴下了
So, how weird was it to see someone who looked exactly like Optimus
这是多么诡异的一件事啊？
kicking the scrap out of you?
那个情景我永远也不会忘记
It's a sight I won't soon forget.
不知道失去了领导人\N机械党是否还会一如既往地继续行动
The question remains whether M.E.C.H. will continue to function as we know it... without its leader.
还里有一个坏消息
Well, here's the kicker.
我们仔细地检查过了
We sifted through the wreckage with a fine-tooth comb...
没有发现任何塞拉斯的踪迹
And couldn't find any trace of Silas.
他的内部脏器严重受损
The internal damage to his organs is massive
常规的医疗水平已经无能为力
and beyond the scope of conventional medicine.
但我们的领袖是幸运的
Fortunately for our leader
因为机械党能打破常规
M.E.C.H. is anything but conventional.